<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Callisto</string>
    <string name="gps_network_not_enabled"> The app requires Location services to run. Would you like to enable them now?</string>
    <string name="open_location_settings">Yes</string>
    <string name="Cancel">No, stay in the menu.</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_not_enabled">The app requires Mobile Data to run. Would you like to enable them now?</string>
    <string name="open_mobile_data_settings">Yes</string>
    <string name="Ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="services_not_enabled">
        The app requires both Mobile Data and Location Services with High Accuracy enabled.\n\n
        Please enable them before continuing.</string>
    <string name="no_sats">
        The app requires both Mobile Data and Location Services with High Accuracy enabled.\n\n
        Try to improve your signal by being in an open area.\n\n
        If no satellites are shown, it is possible your phone does not support access to raw satellite signal.\n\n
        You can still use the app using native Android Location service.</string>
    <string name="gps_sats">
        If no Galileo satellites are shown, it is possible your phone hardware does not support Galileo navigation.\n\n
        You can still use the app wih GPS only.</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        Powered by <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.galfins.gnss_compare">GNSS Compare</a>\n\n

        Created with support from the European Space Agency (ESA) as part of the ESA Galileo App Competition. \n\n

        Made by The ChocolaTeam:\n\n

        Lionel Garcia\nCedric Ia\nMatej Poliaček\nEmilie Udnaes\nPeter Vaník\n\n

        Released open source under the <a href="https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">Apache v 2.0 license</a>.\n\n

        <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Callisto-GAME-1666262033493155/">Callisto Facebook</a> --- <a href="https://github.com/TheChocolateam">The ChocolaTeam Github</a>
    </string>
    <string name="landingGPSInfo">GPS Used: - Visible: -</string>
    <string name="landingGalInfo">GAL Used: - Visible: -</string>

    <!-- BUTTON STRINGS FOR INFO ACTIVITY -->
    <string name="infoDefaultText">Please select a category you would like to learn about, by clicking one of the buttons on the left</string>

    <string name="infoWhatIsGalLabel">What is Galileo?</string>
    <string name="infoWhatIsGalText">Galileo is the global navigation satellite system (GNSS)
                                    created by the European Union (EU) through the European GNSS Agency (GSA).\n\n

                                    One of the aims of Galileo is to provide an independent high-precision positioning so
                                    European nations do not have to rely on the U.S. GPS, or the Russian GLONASS systems,
                                    which could be disabled their operators at any time.\n\n

                                    Galileo is intended to provide position measurements within 1-metre precision,
                                    and to provide a new global search and rescue (SAR) function.\n\n

                                    Galileo started offering Early Operational Capability on 15 December 2016,
                                    with service continuing to improve as more satellites are launched.\n\n

                                    Source and more info: <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Galileo_(satellite_navigation)">Galileo GNSS on Wikipedia</a>
                                    </string>

    <string name="infoCanUseGalLabel">Can I use Galileo?</string>
    <string name="infoCanUseGalText">First available smartphones capable of receiving navigation signal from Galileo satellites became available in 2017.
                                    Therefore, if you bought a new phone after this point in time, there is a possibility it supports Galileo.\n\n

                                    Just like with GPS and other navigation providers, you don\'t need to download an app to benefit from Galileo.
                                    If your phone supports Galileo, the Android operating system in your phone automatically processes it to calculate your position.
                                    If you use e.g. Google Maps, your position is determined based on all available satellites - GPS, Galileo and
                                    others alike, depending on the chips in your phone. In newer phones, developers can access the satellite signals
                                    picked up by the chip separately. This way you can only see results coming from Galileo only, or GPS only - just like in this app.\n\n

                                    You can read more about phones supporting Galileo GNSS <a href="https://www.gsc-europa.eu/galileo-gsc-overview/services/galileo-initial-services/galileo-enabled-devices">here.</a>
                                    </string>

    <string name="infoCanUseRawMLabel">Native navigation? "Raw measurements"?</string>
    <string name="infoCanUseRawMText">Some of the newer phones allow developers access the unprocessed data broadcast by the navigation satellites.
                                    Availability of this feature depends on the device and also on the version of Android used.\n\n

                                    By accesing raw data, developers can use their own calculations and corrections to best fit their needs.
                                    If you would like to compare the differences yourself, try <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.galfins.gnss_compare">GNSS Compare</a> app,
                                    which also powers the navigation aspect of Callisto. You can compare Galileo with GPS, and explore various calculation options.\n\n

                                    If your phone does not support raw GNSS measurements, it means the satellite data is directly processed by Android before
                                    being used in apps. In case of Callisto, you are prompted to use the native navigation present in Android.\n\n

                                    For more technical information, see the <a href="https://developer.android.com/guide/topics/sensors/gnss">Android Developers Documentation on Raw GNSS Measurements</a>
                                    </string>

    <string name="infoESALabel">What is ESA?</string>
    <string name="infoESAText">The European Space Agency (ESA) is an intergovernmental organisation of 22 member states dedicated to the exploration of space.
                            Established in 1975 and headquartered in Paris, France, ESA has a worldwide staff of about 2,200 in 2018 and an annual budget of about €5.6 billion in 2018.\n\n

                            ESA\'s space flight programme includes human spaceflight (mainly through participation in the ISS program); the launch and operation of unmanned exploration
                            missions to other planets and the Moon; Earth observation, science and telecommunication; designing launch vehicles; and maintaining a major spaceport, the Guiana Space Centre at Kourou, French Guiana.\n\n

                            The EU and ESA co-operate on the Galileo satellite navigation system.\n\n

                            <a href="https://www.esa.int/">https://www.esa.int/</a>\n\n

                            Source: <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/European_Space_Agency">ESA on Wikipedia</a>
                            </string>

    <string name="infoGSALabel">What is GSA?</string>
    <string name="infoGSAText">The European Global Navigation Satellite Systems Agency (European GNSS Agency; GSA) is the agency of the European Union (EU) that aims to
                            ensure that essential public interests are properly defended and represented in connection with satellite navigation programmes of the union:
                            Galileo and European Geostationary Navigation Overlay Service (EGNOS).\n\n

                            The agency is responsible for managing and monitoring the use of the program funds. It will help the European Commission deal with
                            any matters relating to satellite radio-navigation.\n\n

                            <a href="https://www.gsa.europa.eu/">https://www.gsa.europa.eu/</a>\n\n

                            Source: <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/European_GNSS_Agency">GSA on Wikipedia</a>
                            </string>
</resources>
